Interviewer: Can you play a musical instrument?
Duncan: I can. I can play the violin.
Interviewer: How well do you play it?
Duncan: Not very.
Interviewer: Do you have noisy neighbours?
Myles: Um, I’m lucky, um, I don’t. But I think I’m the noisy neighbour.
Interviewer: What do you do?
Myles: I play the guitar.
Interviewer: What’s your favourite month of the year? Why?
Tiffany: My favourite month is December because it gets colder,
and I like snow and cold weather.
And I like Christmas time.
Interviewer: What kind of music do you like?
Stephen: A lot of kinds of music. Um, I typically listen to electronic dance, and um, indie rock.
I listen to the new folk, they call it.
But I like opera and a lot of jazz. The list could go on.
Interviewer: What kind of music don’t you like?
Stephen: I don’t like country music.
Interviewer: Do you have a favourite band or singer?
Stephen: Sure. Right now, my favourite band is Wye Oak from Brooklyn.
Interviewer: What kind of books do you like?
Dasha: Um, I read like all sorts of books, from history books to like, novels, and
all sorts of books really.
Interviewer: What are you reading at the moment?
Dasha: Er, at the moment I’m reading a history of modern France.